development: &common_settings
  # use a string to uniquely identify yourself to the API
  api_key: <%= ENV.fetch('TEXTCAPTCHA_API_IDENTIFIER', 'acts_as_textcaptcha_demo') %>
  # only allow 2 minutes before captcha cache expires
  cache_expiry_minutes: 2
  questions:
      - question: 'Is ice hot or cold?'
        answers: 'cold'
      - question: 'what color is an orange?'
        answers: 'orange'
      - question: 'what is two plus 3?'
        answers: '5,five'
      - question: 'what is 5 times two?'
        answers: '10,ten'
      - question: 'How many colors in the list, green, brown, foot and blue?'
        answers: '3,three'
      - question: 'what is Georges name?'
        answers: 'george'
      - question: '11 minus 1?'
        answers: '10,ten'
      - question: 'is boiling water hot or cold?'
        answers: 'hot'
      - question: 'what color is my blue shirt today?'
        answers: 'blue'
      - question: 'what is 16 plus 4?'
        answers: '20,twenty'

test:
  <<: *common_settings

production:
  <<: *common_settings
